When we find it, wanna go with us?
- To do what?
- Party with the pretty girls, dude.
(Leonard:)Are you insane?
You're not gonna party with them.
You're not even gonna get near
that place.
(Howard:)That's what they said to Neil Armstrong
about the moon.
(Sheldon:)No one said anything of the kind
to Neil Armstrong.
(Sheldon:)The entire nation dedicated a decade
of effort and treasure...
(Sheldon:)...to put a man on the moon.
(Howard:)My fellow Americans,
before this year is out...
(Howard:)...we will put a Wolowitz
on one of America's Top Models.
(Raj:)And a large number of people
will believe it never happened.
(Penny(arriving):)Okay, let me guess.
(Penny(arriving):)Quesadilla with soy cheese...
- ...for lactose-intolerant Leonard.
- Thank you.
(Penny:)Shrimp caesar salad with no almonds
for the highly allergic...
(Penny:)...kosher-only-on-the-High-Holidays
Howard.
(Penny:)And for our
suddenly-back-on-the-Hindu-wagon Raj...
...meat lover's pizza, no meat.
(Penny:)Coming right up.
(Sheldon:)Wait. Excuse me. You forgot
my barbecue bacon cheeseburger...
(Sheldon:)...barbecue sauce,
bacon and cheese on the side.